<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Samantha Mathis & Jacob Hurley-->
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NoRegrets</string>
    <string name="help">How To Use NoRegrets"\n"</string>
    <string name="info">This app is to help protect you from yourself.
        Ever send a drunk text and regretting immediately afterwards? "\n\n" Use this app to send all
        messages. "\n\n" First go to settings and set your difficulty level. If you are sober then you\'ll get easier
        questions to answer before being allowed to send a text. If you drunk be honest and click
        the drunk difficulty which will make the questions you have to answer harder. "\n\n" After
        you have set the difficulty you may choose your theme dark or light mode in settings. Your
        preference will be saved everytime you open up the app click the button again to switch
        themes. "\n\n" Another feature in settings will allow you to look back at your most recent results.
        It will show your past 20 questions that you have answered and whether you answered correctly.
        "\n\n" Once you have set up your customizations you may go back to the home page and begin. "\n\n"
        You will be sent to a page with a question you must answer the question,  You will be given a set
        of five questions, if you miss more than one question then a timer will appear and you must
        wait out the time before trying again. "\n\n" Once you have answered at least four questions
        correctly it will direct you to a list of your previous conversations, you may click on one of those
        or click the new message button. "\n\n" The new message will direct you to a list of your contacts where
        you can start a new conversation. Otherwise it will direct you to your conversation with the person
        you chose. Here it acts like a normal messaging app. Where you can send texts, images, or drawings.
        "\n\n" Enjoy and Stay Safe. "\n\n"
    </string>
</resources>